To be continued...
Enough! I can't even hear myself think!
If you're not here to work, then go home!
What do you think, Julie?
Who the hell do you think you're talking to, Mia?
Sorry, you're right. We'll try to keep the noise down as long as we're all in the classroom.
Hey, Srono.
What do you think you're talking to?
Hey, give it a rest. No need to pick on that poor turtle.
Huh? Hell are you supposed to be?
Oh, wait. I think that might be Quackmire.
It doesn't matter who started it. Only cowards gang up like that.
Huh. Let's go.
Are you all right?
At what point did it sound like I wanted your...
Sorry. I'm fine. Thank you.
Yeah, no problem at all.
I figured he was going to snap at me.
Has he finally realized I'm not his enemy?
What'd I do to upset him so much in the first place?
Well, whatever.
Hey.
So, um, there's this girl I like.
Okay.
Is it me? It's not me, right?
Maybe he just wants help writing a love letter or something.
Yeah.
That's her there.
Oh, good for...
You poor guy.
That is my love.
Lady Alina Lee's Dragon Road.
A name nearly as beautiful and bold as the woman who bears it.
She's studious as her grades can attest.
And as an adventurer, she grasps the practicalities of magical combat.
How I admire her!
Uh-huh.
I hoped I was mistaken, but nope.
He really does mean Alina Lee's.
Oof.
There have been some scurrilous rumors about her taking any male student who looks at her twice as a lover.
And some of the professors as well.
I've tried to intervene, but...
Sorry, bud, but those were no rumors.
So, what do you want me to do?
Oh, well, you know her, right?
So, would you...
Mind introducing us?
Romantic advice?
Uh, why?
Do you have a crush on someone?
No, but a classmate of mine does.
Who's that?
As long as this stays between us, it's Cliff, one of the other special students.
Oh, yes, I know him.
Please, continue.
The way he tells it, he fell in love with this woman immediately, at first sight.
And I'm kind of close with the person he fell for, but I'm not sure about introducing them.
I just don't want him to think it's because I want her to myself.
Do you have any idea how I should navigate this?
Well, I suppose I should ask, where does your hesitation come from?
I have nothing against her, but she has some issues that make her a tricky match.
I see.
You know, even if a trait is unappealing to you, that doesn't necessarily mean it would be to Cliff.
From what I hear, most people couldn't imagine dating the person I like, but...
Master Fitz has a crush?
I wonder who it is.
Princess Ariel is probably the safest bet.
And it's hard to see someone around all the time and feel like they're out of reach.
So yeah, I'd say, go ahead and introduce them in that way.
He would at least have an opportunity to express himself.
You think?
I'm afraid that could lead to all sorts of trouble down the road.
That's not your burden, though.
I mean, once you get them in a room together, they have to figure out the next steps for themselves.
Yeah, he does kind of have a point there.
I guess you're right.
Thank you, Master Fitz.
I appreciate the input.
Oh, please.
I'm just glad I was able to help at all.
So...
Hey there, Rudeus.
What a lovely surprise.
You don't often call on me.
And who is this?
All right, good luck in there.
Just remember I did warn you.
So if this goes poorly in any way, please don't take that out on me.
Of course.
I'm fully prepared for rejection.
Hello, Alina-Lise.
I would like you to meet Cliff Grimoire.
He's one of the special students and a year ahead of me.
It's an honor, my lady.
As he said, I am Cliff.
Oh, my.
What a perfect gentleman you are.
My name's Alina-Lise Dragonroad.
Now then, what brings you to see me this fine afternoon, Master Cliff?
He's been interested in meeting you for some time, so I thought I'd introduce you.
Indeed.
I've spent many an evening admiring your radiant beauty from across the courtyard.
I beg you to consider a personal relationship with me.
Huh?
Really?
Really what?
How much do you want for him?
She thinks I'm here to pimp my upperclassmen?
Now that's low.
That's not what this is.
You can't mean that.
Rudeus, you know what I'm like.
I really can't commit to anyone.
Why would you bring this naive little choir boy here?
That's just cruel.
Now I'm the shameless one?
I'm not trying to trick him.
I am just introducing him like he asked me to.
You mean it?
Yeah, I'll even swear by Master Roxy if you like.
Well, if he's serious, that's also a problem.
People shouldn't have feelings for me.
That's a surprise.
I figured she'd say that she had an in-or-something book just in case and whisk him away.
You didn't forget about my curse, did you?
It's not compatible with an exclusive relationship.
Yeah, that's too bad, isn't it?
Guess you'll just have to turn him down.
You wouldn't mind?
That won't cause any bad blood between you two?
Nope, it's not a problem.
But I do think you should tell him exactly why.
I can do that.
Rudeus, please see yourself out so that Cliff and I may speak in private.
Huh?
Oh, yeah, of course.
Excuse me, I'll be just outside.
And Rudeus?
Thank you, I mean that.
The gratitude in his voice makes my chest ache.
Hey, Zanobar, are you here?
Ha, good morning, Rudeus.
As you can clearly see, we've chosen to become a couple.
Okay, why?
There was such a fire and passion to his proposal that it pierced and melted even my most frozen heart of hearts.
Congratulations, I'm happy for you.
But what about your curse?
A curse is nothing in the face of true love.
For Cliff's sake, I'll do my best to control myself.
If your heart belongs to me, nothing else matters.
And I swear to you, I will lift your curse one day.
Oh, Cliff.
Oh, Adlina Lise.
If this works for them, then who am I to interfere?
And if I'm being honest, I would also love to break my curse and get busy with someone.
Wow, they're so intense.
All is upon us, and Beast Folk mating rituals are in full swing.
Namely, a one-on-one duel that acts as a marriage proposal and determines who will lead the resulting family.
In other words, they're in heat.
Which brings me to my two absent classmates.
Lenia and Persina are princesses of the Doldia tribe.
The Beast Folk all adore them, and despite their public disinterest in marriage, they're inundated with challenges from suitors every year.
So they wrote to let me know that they wouldn't be leaving the girls' dorm for a while.
But they also said, the rest is up to you.
And I don't know what that means.
I take it that you, sir, are Quagmire Rudeus.
I challenge you to a matrimonial duel.
Is this one of those proposal challenges that have been kind of in vogue around campus lately, or...?
Indeed.
I beg your pardon, but I'm actually straight, you see, so I'm gonna be going...
You have no right to refuse!
I wrote to Lady Persina, and she informed me that you're the boss of her pack.
Thus, you are duty-bound to accept all challengers.
Oh, that's what they meant.
Jerks.
Now draw your weapon!
Well, better luck next year, I suppose.
Hey, Rudeus.
Have you seen this line outside?
What did you do?
I didn't do anything, but apparently whoever beats me gets to marry Linia and or Persina.
No, really?
There's no way you have the authority to allow that.
That's for the chief of the Doldia tribe to decide.
Well, they've been redirecting all their personal challenges to me either way.
Gauntlet of highly motivated horny alpha males, here I come!
Oh, well, it isn't all men, from what I could see.
There was at least one girl out there.
Wait, really?
Is she cute?
Wow.
You really are your father's son.
Hey, sorry, what'd you say?
Hey, Master Fitz!
Ugh!
What the heck?
Your courage is a credit to you.
This university of magic attracts some truly stout-hearted fellows.
What, uh...
Hmm?
Heh heh.
Hello!
They said I had to defeat them all if I didn't want to wait my turn to see you.
And here you are, right on cue.
Yes, the Eye of Foresight.
You must be Rudeus Greyrat.
My fiancée, Kishirika Kishirisu, great emperor of the demon world, speaks well of you.
I am the demon king, Barigari.
And I've come to challenge you to a duel.
What is happening?
Hmm.
Must we wait?
Forgive me.
Someone is on their way to fetch my staff for me right now.
You humans can be so hasty.
I expected to be shooed away.
But you seem quite composed.
No wonder my fiancée thinks so highly of you.
And you said...
Your fiancée is Empress Kishirika, didn't you?
Yes.
Her majesty bestowed this demon eye on me, though we only met briefly.
She described you as something of a magical marvel.
She hasn't spoken of anyone with such excitement in a long while.
I'm no one special.
I may have a bit more mana than the average person, but...
Please be seated.
More marvelous than Laplace.
That's how she first described you to me, without a moment's hesitation.
She's never said that of anyone else before,
which means your mana capacity must be among the greatest in the world.
Wow, is that so?
Granted, I have been training non-stop to improve it for most of my life now.
No amount of training would allow you or anyone else to rival Laplace.
For most, it's simply impossible.
Okay.
Even if most people can't do it, what about reincarnated people like me?
Maybe the man-god hooked me up with some sweet hacks or something.
Come to think of it, your majesty, may I ask you about a certain name?
And, um, to be clear, I'm not an agent or a minion or anything of this person I'm thinking about,
so please don't attack me for simply mentioning them, if you wouldn't mind?
I said begin our duel until you're armed.
You have the Demon King's word.
Does the name man-god mean anything at all to you?
Man-god?
How is it that you came to learn this name, boy?
They appear in my dreams.
Hmm, in your dreams, huh?
I see.
What do you know about them?
Hmm, nothing.
Ah, that's too bad.
Indeed.
What a sad fellow you are.
Clamming up all of a sudden.
Laugh with me, boy!
Here's your staff. I'm sorry it took so long to find it.
No, that's quite all right. I appreciate you running to get it.
Please don't do anything rash. If it looks like you'll lose, just grovel and beg for mercy.
No one will think less of you for it, I promise.
Your Majesty?
Call me Body Boy.
Uh, sir, Body, then. I have a request.
Speak your piece.
Even if I lose to you, I would ask that you please spare my life.
Begging for mercy before we begin. You're a funny one, aren't you?
Life is a tragic thing to waste.
You're so sure you'll lose. One would think such a large monopool would lend a man some confidence.
About two years ago, I fought a man known as the Dragon God and barely made it out alive.
Crap. He didn't react to the name Man God, but does he know Orsted?
I think I might have hit a nerve.
All right. I have a proposal for the terms of our duel.
What might that be?
Just one blow.
Huh?
Strike me once. Attack me with the force of your mightiest blow.
Perhaps use a spell you used against the Dragon God.
If you can manage to wound me, then you will be named the Victor.
That sounds reasonable. I accept your conditions.
Good.
Against Orsted, I was unarmed, one-handed, and panicking.
But here, I can channel everything I have into this shot.
Creating the bullet is fundamentally no different than crafting a figure.
I'll focus on hardness and aerodynamics, then rotate it.
The faster I can make it spin, the better penetration it will have on contact.
But velocity is the most critical aspect.
I've never used this much mana for speed before.
All right. Get ready.
Excellent. Go on.
No way.
Is he dead?
Buddy Daddy has revived!
Oh, you're alive.
Yes, I thought I was a goner!
You've vanquished me in single combat, Brutus.
So you may call yourself a hero.
I don't think I will, but thanks.
Then at least let out a victory cheer for the crowd.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Okay.
If he says I won, I guess I won.
Um, I'm the winner!
Well done!
Now it's my turn to take a whack.
Huh?
Ha ha!
Ha ha ha!
There.
Is the pain gone, too?
Yeah, it is.
Thank you.
Well, healing aside, after the day you just had, I would advise taking it easy tonight.
I really can't thank you enough for all your help, Master Fitz.
He's probably right.
Between duels and Demon Kings, I've had one hell of a day.
But hey, at least I'll probably never see Body Gotti again.
I'm you, you could do it, boss!
A whole mating season, and we didn't even have to lift a finger!
But I never expected a Demon King would show up to challenge you for our hand.
I suppose our charms really must reach all corners of the world.
Well, as thanks, I invite you to touch Lenea's boobs.
Thank you.
That's very generous.
Yee-haw!
Huh?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
The immortal Demon King Body Gotti has returned!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Goddamn it.
La-ya-la-ya-la